bbinary.com 2012-12-05

# Welcome to Banc De Binary - About us

Our Privacy Statement sets out the basis on which we process any personal data that we collect from you. If you have any questions, we are here to help 24/7. 

## What Personal Information do we collect?

If you deal with Banc De Binary as a private client or otherwise in your individual capacity relating to a trust or investment vehicle established to invest on your behalf, then typically we collect the following types of personal data about you:

  1. Personal details, such as name, age, occupation and marital status.
  2. Contact details such as address, telephone, email, in some cases both private and work-related contact details.
  3. Identification documents, such as your passport, copies which may generally include a head and shoulders photograph from, as applicable, your passport, national identity card or driver's license, as required by laws and regulations addressing due diligence and related matters.
  4. A personal identifier, depending on your country of residence.
  5. Extensive financial information, including source of wealth, investment experience and objectives, risk tolerance and, in certain jurisdictions, representations required under applicable law or regulation concerning your financial resources. 

If you deal with Banc De Binary in the capacity of an officer, employee, director and/or principal of one of our corporate or institutional clients, the typical personal data we collect about you personally would include:

  1. Your name and contact details
  2. Your role/position/title and area of responsibility
  3. Certain identifying information (e.g. passport photo, etc.) as required by laws and regulations addressing money laundering and related matters.  

You are not required to supply any of the personal data that we may request. However failure to supply any of the personal data that we request may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you or your company. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

## How do we collect your personal information?

Typically we obtain personal data about you in the forms and documents used when you apply for an account with us, when you engage in transactions with us, when you access or use our products and services, or from third parties authorized to provide us with such information. We also collect personal data when we monitor or record our communications with you or through use of certain technology as detailed further below.

## What are the purposes for which we use your Personal Data?

We, our associated firms and/or other persons acting on our or their behalf may process and use your personal data to:

  * Administer and operate services in accordance with the customer documents, including authorizing or confirming transactions.
  * Carry out credit, money laundering and conflict checks and for fraud prevention purposes (and this may include consideration of information regarding political affiliations and criminal offenses committed or alleged to have been committed) and to contact you about other services and products we offer.
  * Exercise and defend our legal rights.
  * Comply with legal and regulatory obligations and requests anywhere in the world (including reporting to and being audited by national and international regulatory, enforcement or exchange bodies and complying with court orders).
  * Record or monitor communications, (including email, instant messaging, facsimile, telephone and other electronic communications), with you or your agent(s) for quality control and security purposes, as a record of your orders, instructions and related matters and in order to comply (and monitor compliance) with applicable laws and regulations, our agreements and any applicable policies and procedures; and as otherwise permitted under any applicable law or regulation.

## How do we use Cookies and similar technology?

Banc De Binary uses certain technology on its websites to collect information from visitors and compiles aggregate statistical information about how visitors use our websites, including information relating to the frequency of visits, IP addresses, the average length of visits, which pages are viewed during a visit, and the effectiveness of advertising on our websites.

Banc De Binary uses this information to improve the website content and performance. No individually identifiable information is collected for this purpose and Banc De Binary does not monitor individual visitor behavior. Information held in cookies set by Banc De Binary is kept to a minimum and can only be read by Banc De Binary or by someone who has physical access to your personal computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us to estimate our audience size and usage pattern, to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests, to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log in to our site.

## How can you opt out of Banc De Binary’s mailing list? 

If you do not wish to receive any communications from Banc De Binary you may opt out of our mailing list by sending an email indicating this to: privacy@bbinary.com. 

## When do we Disclose Personal Data we collect about you? 

Please be assured that Banc De Binary does not sell, rent or trade your personal data. Banc De Binary does not disclose your personal data, except as described in this Privacy Statement. Furthermore, third parties who process your personal data on our behalf are required to adhere to confidentiality standards with respect to such information. Our processing and use of your personal data, for the purposes specified in this Privacy Statement, may include disclosure of your personal data: 

  * Between us and our associated firms, a list of which may be consulted in the corporate website of Banc De Binary.
  * To other persons processing your personal data on our or their behalf or otherwise providing us or them with professional or other services.
  * To third parties such as settlement agents, overseas banks or exchange or clearing houses to whom we disclose in the course of providing products and services to you.
  * To credit reference, fraud prevention and other similar agencies, and other financial institutions, with whom information To persons to whom we assign or novate our rights or obligations.
  * To prospective sellers or buyers in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets or if all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * To national and international regulatory, enforcement or exchange bodies or courts anywhere in the world as required by applicable law or regulations anywhere in the world or at their request.

## How do we protect the Security and Confidentiality of the personal data we collect about you? 

Banc De Binary maintains appropriate physical, technical and procedural safeguards to protect any information that you provide to us from accidental or unauthorized loss, misuse, damage, modification, access or disclosure. 

## Banc De Binary has established an Information Security Team, which leads efforts to: 

  * Safeguard the confidentiality and privacy of information resources
  * Properly classify information resources.
  * Meet legal and regulatory obligations concerning the protection of information resources.
  * Implement and maintain information security policies and procedures. 
  * Integrate protection of information resources into the process life cycles of the business.
  * Educate those working for or on behalf of Banc De Binary on information security policies and responsibilities.
  * Authenticate users and limit access to information resources based on authorization that has been granted. 

## What rights do you have under European Data Protection Laws? 

If you wish to access a copy of your personal data, or you wish to modify any personal data we hold about you, or you want us to cease processing any of your personal data held by us and/or our associated firms, you can do so by written request to the our Data Protection Counsel at the address set out below. In the case of a request for access to personal data, we and our associated firms reserve the right to charge an appropriate fee, if applicable. You may be required to supply a valid means of identification as a security precaution to assist us in preventing the unauthorized disclosure of your personal data. We will process your request within the time provided by applicable law. 

## How do we update this Privacy Statement? 

We may change or update portions of this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our practices and or applicable law and regulation. Please check this Privacy Statement from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the Privacy Statement, which may be indicated by a change in the effective date noted at the beginning of the Privacy Statement.
